<resources>
    <string name="app_name">YourLifeIsMyLife</string>
    <string name="intro_page_one">Share Your Psychological condition with your family , your friend , your partner life by measuring ٍSerotonin and Dopamine levels.</string>
    <string name="intro_page_two">Share Your Location with your family , your friend , your life partner </string>
    <string name="intro_page_three">Thinking Positively with morning messages every day</string>
    <string name="intro_page_four">Guiding you to Tools for Cognitive Behavioral Therapy, and more.</string>

    <string name="knowledge_page_one">
        "-The normal range for Serotonin levels in your blood. 101 - 283 nanograms per milliliter (ng/mL) and The normal range for Dopamine is 0 to 30 pg/mL (195.8 pmol/L).
-however, may differ slightly depending on the measurements and samples tested and activity

-if one of these values or both decrease about the normal value , members of circle will get notification automatically  and your life is my life will direct them to  some techniques to help you💙

-As low level of these neurotransmitters can cause Mental illnesses include depression, anxiety disorders, schizophrenia, eating disorders, ocd and addictive behaviors."
    </string>
    <string name="knowledge_page_two">
        "if the value of serotonin level decrease about the normal value and getting notification you should begin same techniques

1- Relaxation and stress reduction techniques deep breathing exercises muscle relaxation.

2- Successive approximation: Each successive step builds upon the previous steps so you gain confidence as you go bit by bit

3- Exercise

4 - Eat dark chocolate
    </string>

    <string name="knowledge_page_three_image">"5- Food: Eat Foods Rich in Omega 3 Fatty Acids Growing evidence suggests that omega-3 fatty acids (abundant on oily fish such as sardines, salmon, and mackerel)"</string>
    <string name="knowledge_page_three_image2">"Whole grains are important sources of B vitamins, nutrients vital for brain health."</string>
    <string name="knowledge_page_three">
        "6 - Getting into the outdoors, especially around trees.

7 - going to a therapist

By these steps you can protect your family and your friend and your life partner from depression and another mental illness  that may lead to suicide."
    </string>
    <string name="title_activity_maps">Map</string>
    <string name="measurements_desc">
        "An economical and simple smart band that measure automatic serotonin and dopamine levels.
When you connect your band to the application it will measure dopamine and serotonin levels automatically"
        </string>
    <string name="knowledge_page_two_title">"If values of Serotonin &amp; Dopamine levels decrease about the normal values,

Some techniques should be done for healing As low level of these neurotransmitters can cause Mental illnesses these Techniques."</string>

</resources>