<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Your Life Is My Life</string>
    <string name="intro_page_one">Share Your Psychological condition with your family , your friend , your partner life by measuring ٍSerotonin and Dopamine levels.</string>
    <string name="intro_page_two">Share Your Location with your family , your friend , your life partner </string>
    <string name="intro_page_three">Thinking Positively with morning messages every day</string>
    <string name="intro_page_four">Guiding you to Tools for Cognitive Behavioral Therapy, and more.</string>

    <string name="knowledge_page_one">
        "-The normal range for Serotonin levels in your blood. 101 - 283 nanograms per milliliter (ng/mL) and The normal range for Dopamine is 0 to 30 pg/mL (195.8 pmol/L).
-however, may differ slightly depending on the measurements and samples tested and activity

-if one of these values or both decrease about the normal value , Head of circle will get notification automatically  and your life is my life will direct them to  some techniques to help you💙

-As low level of these neurotransmitters can cause Mental illnesses include depression, anxiety disorders, schizophrenia, eating disorders, ocd and addictive behaviors."
    </string>
    <string name="knowledge_page_two">
        "1- Relaxation and stress reduction techniques deep breathing exercises muscle relaxation.

2- Successive approximation: Each successive step builds upon the previous steps so you gain confidence as you go bit by bit

3- Exercise

4 - Eat dark chocolate
    </string>

    <string name="knowledge_page_three_image">"5- Food: Eat Foods Rich in Omega 3 Fatty Acids Growing evidence suggests that omega-3 fatty acids (abundant on oily fish such as sardines, salmon, and mackerel)"</string>
    <string name="knowledge_page_three_image2">"Whole grains are important sources of B vitamins, nutrients vital for brain health."</string>
    <string name="knowledge_page_three">
        "
        6 - Getting into the outdoors, especially around trees.

7 - going to a therapist

By these steps you can protect your family and your friend and your life partner from depression and another mental illness  that may lead to suicide."
    </string>
    <string name="title_activity_maps">Map</string>
    <string name="measurements_desc">
        "An economical and simple smart band that measure automatic serotonin and dopamine levels.
When you connect your band to the application it will measure dopamine and serotonin levels automatically"
        </string>
    <string name="knowledge_page_two_title">"If values of Serotonin &amp; Dopamine levels decrease about the normal values,

Some techniques should be done for healing As low level of these neurotransmitters can cause Mental illnesses.
These Techniques:"</string>

    <string name="knowledge_page_four_title">"If values of Serotonin &amp; Dopamine levels increases more than the normal value , Head of the circle will get notification automatically and then Your Life Is My Life will direct them to some side effects of increasing these neurotransmitters on health to start assisting you 💙"</string>

    <string name="knowledge_page_four_title_two">"The side effects of increasing these neurotransmitters (Serotonin &amp; Dopamine) on health:"</string>

    <string name="knowledge_page_four">
        "1 - Serotonin Syndrome:
-Drugs that cause your serotonin levels to climb and collect in your body can lead to serotonin syndrome. The syndrome can typically occur after you start taking a new drug or increase the dosage of an existing medication.

-The Symptoms of Serotonin syndrome include: Shivering/ Diarrhea/ Headache/ Confusion/ Dilated pupils/ Goose bumps.

-Severe symptoms can include: Twitching muscles/ A loss of muscle agility/ Muscle stiffness/ High fever rapid heart rate/ High blood pressure/ Irregular heartbeat/ Seizures

    </string>

    <string name="knowledge_page_five_one">
        "Treatment
        (Going to therapist to treat you ,As serotonin syndrome symptoms will disappear within a day if dr describes to take medication that blocks serotonin or replace the drug that’s causing the condition ,so you should take care as Serotonin syndrome can be life-threatening if left untreated )."
    </string>

    <string name="knowledge_page_five_two">
        "2 - increasing of serotonin is tumor marker of gastrointestinal carcinoid, hepatic and ovarian carcinoid ."
    </string>

    <string name="knowledge_page_five_three">
        "Treatment
(You should go to examination to detect any problems  in your health and treat it before being more dangerous)."
    </string>

    <string name="knowledge_page_five_four">
        "3 - High level of dopamine linked to being more competitive, aggressive and having poor impulse control, It can lead to conditions that include ADHD, binge eating, addiction , so it is an indicator for addictive personality ."
    </string>


    <string name="knowledge_page_five_five">
        "Treatment
        (You should go to examination to detect any problems  in your health to treat it before being more dangerous And go to therapist to save addictive person who may be dangerous to self and others )."
    </string>

    <string name="privacy_policy_url">https://pages.flycricket.io/your-life-is-my-life-1/privacy.html</string>


</resources>